Register of the Bonner Frank Fellers Papers, 1904-1997
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings II, 1922-1972. (Box 27-37)
  - Outline of lecture on World War II, undated. (Folder 29: 8)
  - Outline of talk, U.S. Military Academy, West Point, New York, undated. (Folder 29: 9)
  - Outline of talk on air power, undated. (Folder 29: 10)
  - Outline of talk on American foreign policy, undated. (Folder 29: 11)
  - "Peace Cannot Be Bought,", undated. (Folder 29: 12)
  - "Philippine Problems,", undated. (Folder 29: 13)
  - "Planning for a Better Defense without Killing the Taxpayers,", undated. (Folder 29: 14)
  - "The Problem of Japan,", undated. (Folder 29: 15)
  - Radio broadcast on role of air power, undated. (Folder 29: 16)
  - "Random Observations on Projected Foreign Trade Zone in Manila,", undated. (Folder 29: 17)
  - "Reasons for the Cancellation of the Treaty between Great Britain and Egypt,", undated. (Folder 29: 18)
  - "The Rise of the Philippine Independence Idea,", undated. (Folder 29: 19)
  - "A Romance and a Boy's Resolution,", undated. (Folder 29: 20)
  - "Shark Fancier Will Swim to Prove 'Em Harmless,", undated. (Folder 29: 21)
  - "Sino Japanese War,", undated. (Folder 29: 22)
  - Speech on air power, undated. (Folder 29: 23)
  - Speech on American military strategy, undated. (Folder 29: 24)
  - Speech on the Philippines during World War II, undated. (Folder 29: 25)
  - Speech on treatment of prisoners of war, undated. (Folder 29: 26)
  - Story, undated. (Folder 29: 27)
  - "The Strategy of Power Allocation,", undated. (Folder 29: 28)
  - "StrategyProvince of the People,", undated. (Folder 29: 29)
  - "Suggested Draft for a Right-wing A.D.A. Program,", undated. (Folder 29: 30)
  - "Suggested Outline for Philippine Pamphlet,", undated. (Folder 29: 31)
  - "SurveyUnion of Soviet Socialist Republics," lecture, undated. (Folder 29: 32)
  - "Test Mobilization,", undated. (Folder 29: 33)
  - "The True Story of Japan's Surrender,", undated. (Folder 29: 34)
  - "Washington as a Soldier,", undated. (Folder 29: 35)
  - "We Are Headed for War,", undated. (Folder 29: 36)
  - "We Plan Disaster,", undated. (Folder 29: 37)
  - "Western Hemisphere Defense,", undated. (Folder 29: 38)
  - "What Is a Conservative,", undated. (Folder 29: 39)
  - "What Mr. McNamara Meant,", undated. (Folder 29: 40)
  - "Wherein Lies Our Salvation,", undated. (Folder 29: 41)
  - Writing on modern warfare, undated. (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - Writing on psychological warfare, undated. (Folder 30: 2)
  - "Travel Notes,", 1922-1939. (Folder 30: 3)
  - "Meredith,", 1929. (Folder 30: 4)
  - The Psychology of the Japanese Soldier, 1935
    - Holograph (Folder 30: 5)
    - Typescript (Folder 30: 6)
    - Printed copy (Folder 30: 7)
  - "Tomorrow's Army," Chemical Warfare Bulletin, 1936 January
    - Typescript and correspondence (Folder 30: 8)
    - Printed copy (Folder 30: 9)
  - "The Philippine Army,", 1939 April 8. (Folder 30: 10)
  - "Notes on the Far East," lecture, 1939 December 18. (Folder 30: 11)
  - "Your Foreign Service Tour in the Philippines,", circa 1940. (Folder 30: 12)
  - "The Philippines," lecture, 1940 March 27-28. (Folder 30: 13)
  - Outline for lecture on World War II, Hartford, Connecticut, 1940 June 12. (Folder 30: 14)
  - "Estimate of the Situation with Especial Reference to the Middle East,", 1943 March 12. (Folder 30: 15)
  - Answer to Japan, 1944 July 1
    - Printed copy (Folder 30: 16)
    - Proposed revision version (Folder 30: 17)
  - "Notes from Discussion on World Affairs,", 1944 August 20. (Folder 30: 18)
  - "Notes from Discussion on Russia,", 1944 August 27. (Folder 30: 19)
    Correspondence and typescript
  - "Notes from Discussion on the SWPA,", 1944 September 10. (Folder 30: 20)
  - "Army Hour," radio broadcast, 1944 November 5. (Folder 30: 21)
  - "Peace from the Palace,", 1946
    - Notes (Folder 30: 22)
    - Typescript drafts (Folder 30: 23-25)
  - "Notes on the American International Position,", 1946 September 25. (Folder 30: 26)
  - "Hirohito's Struggle to Surrender," Foreign Service, 1947 July (Box 31)
    - Typescript (Folder 31: 1)
    - Abridged version, Reader's Digest, 1947 July. (Folder 31: 2)
    - Japanese translation, Reader's Digest (Japanese edition), 1947 September. (Folder 31: 3)
    - Correspondence (Folder 31: 4)
  - "U.S. Airpower Key to Peace," transcript of radio interview, 1947 August 14. (Folder 31: 5)
  - "Our National Security," radio address, Cleveland, Ohio, 1947 September 8. (Folder 31: 6)
  - Radio interview, National Aviation Forum, 1947 October 4. (Folder 31: 7)
  - "The VFW Stand for the Retrievement[sic] of American Air Supremacy," address, National Aeronautical Association, Washington, D.C., 1947 October 21. (Folder 31: 8)
  - "Our National Security," National Bulletin, 1947 December. (Folder 31: 9)
  - "Notes on Our National Security,", 1947 December 30. (Folder 31: 10)
  - Statement on H.R. 5004, Committee on the Judiciary, House of Representatives, Washington, D.C., 1948. (Folder 31: 11)
  - "Our New Friends, the Japanese," Nation's Business, 1948 February. (Folder 31: 12)
  - "Can We Win Our Psychological War with Stalin?", 1948 May 1. (Folder 31: 13)
  - "Our National Security,", 1948 August 4. (Folder 31: 14)
  - "Our National Security," radio address, Cleveland, Ohio, 1948 August 14. (Folder 31: 15)
  - 'Thought War' against the Kremlin, 1949. (Folder 31: 16)
  - "Underlying Military Problems of the Far East," address, School of Advanced International Studies, Washington, D.C., 1949 February 25. (Folder 31: 17)
  - "The Military Assistance Program," Human Events, 1949 July 27. (Folder 31: 18)
    Correspondence, typescript, printed copy, and reprint in Congressional Record, 1949 August 3
  - Testimony, Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Washington, D.C., 1949 August 17. (Folder 31: 19)
    Correspondence, typescript, and printed transcript in Congressional Record, 1949 August 17
  - "Russia's Atomic Explosion," Human Events, 1949 October 5. (Folder 31: 20)
  - "The Korean Blunder,", circa 1950. (Folder 31: 21)
  - Review of Robert L. Eichelberger, Our Jungle Road to Tokyo, circa 1950. (Folder 31: 22)
  - Speech, Battle of Monmouth commemoration, Monmouth, New Jersey, circa 1950. (Folder 31: 23)
  - "Victory without War,", 1950. (Box-folder 32: 1-2)
    Typescript drafts
  - "JapanFriend or Enemy?" radio address, 1950 February 22. (Folder 32: 3)
  - "Significance of the Overt Act in the Field of National Security," lecture, Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Alabama, 1950 April 28. (Folder 32: 4)
  - Speech, Armed Forces Day, Danville, Illinois, 1950 May 20. (Folder 32: 5)
  - Memorial Day address, Rochester, New York, 1950 May 27. (Folder 32: 6)
  - "On Cold War," Human Events, 1950 June 7. (Folder 32: 7)
  - "What Price the Philippines?" Human Events, 1950 July 12
    - Correspondence, typescript, and printed copy (Folder 32: 8)
    - Reprint, Philippine Armed Forces Journal, 1950 August. (Folder 32: 9)
  - "After Korea...What?" radio interview, 1950 July 15. (Folder 32: 10)
  - Speech, Victory Day service, Detroit, Michigan, 1950 August 13. (Folder 32: 11)
  - "How We Can Lick Stalin," Collier's, 1950 September 16
    - Correspondence (Folder 32: 12)
    - Typescript (Folder 32: 13)
    - Printed copy (Folder 32: 14)
  - "The Lessons of Korea," The Freeman, 1950 October 2. (Folder 32: 15)
  - Address, District of Columbia Republican Club rally, Washington, D.C., 1950 October 30. (Folder 32: 16)
  - "Gathering Storm," The Freeman, 1950 October 30. (Folder 32: 17)
  - "How to Make the Russians Revolt," Coronet, 1950 November
    - Correspondence (Folder 32: 18)
    - Typescript and printed copy (Folder 32: 19)
  - "How We Can Lick Stalin," speech, Middlesex, Massachusetts, 1950 November 3. (Folder 32: 20)
    Program only
  - Address, Beacon Society, Boston, Massachusetts, 1950 November 4. (Folder 32: 21)
  - "How We Can Lick the Kremlin," address, annual meeting, Life Insurance Agency Management Association, Chicago, Illinois, 1950 November 16. (Folder 32: 22)
  - "Japan in Surrender," The Freeman, 1950 December 11. (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - "Egypt vs. Britain,", 1951. (Folder 33: 2)
  - "The Veteran and the Coming Election," Young Republican Federation News, vol. 2, no. 2, 1951. (Folder 33: 3)
  - "Our Combat Divisions," Nation's Business, 1951 January. (Folder 33: 4)
  - "The Real Deterrent," Human Events, 1951 January 24. (Folder 33: 5)
    Correspondence and printed copy
  - Review of Desmond Young, Rommel, the Desert Fox, circa 1951 February. (Folder 33: 6)
  - "The Strategic Middle East," Egypt, 1951 February. (Folder 33: 7)
  - Lincoln Day address, Salisbury, Maryland, 1951 February 10. (Folder 33: 8)
  - "Why War with Russia?" address, Rockford, Illinois, 1951 March 9. (Folder 33: 9)
  - Notes prepared for Douglas MacArthur, 1951 April. (Folder 33: 10)
  - "Strategic Concepts and National Objectives," lecture, Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Alabama, 1951 April 11. (Folder 33: 11)
  - "New Foreign Policy...Why Fight Russia," Surplus Record, 1951 June. (Folder 33: 12)
  - "AfricaAnd Our Security," The Freeman, 1951 August 13. (Folder 33: 13)
    Correspondence, typescript, and printed copy
  - Radio address, Morristown, New Jersey, 1951 August 25. (Folder 33: 14)
  - "Will Inflation Win for Stalin?" address, annual meeting, Texas Manufacturers Association, San Antonio, Texas, 1951 October 19. (Folder 33: 15)
  - "Suggested Draft for an Editorial,", 1952. (Folder 33: 16)
  - "How Stalin Can Win," American Mercury, 1952 January. (Folder 33: 17)
  - "Emergency in the Air," Human Events, 1952 January 23. (Folder 33: 18)
  - "Strategic Concepts and War Objectives," lecture, Air War College, Maxwell Air Force Base, Alabama, 1952 February 25. (Folder 33: 19)
  - Speech, Danville, Illinois, 1952 March 7. (Folder 33: 20)
    Clipping and program only
  - "The Overriding IssueDefense," Human Events, 1952 June 18. (Folder 33: 21)
  - "A Suggested Front Page Editorial for Delegates,", 1952 July 9. (Folder 33: 22)
  - "A New Look at War," Air University Quarterly, 1953-1954 Winter. (Folder 33: 23)
  - Wings for Peace, 1953 (Box 34)
    - Correspondence (Folder 34: 1-6)
    - Typescript drafts (Folder 34: 7-8)
    - Proofs (Box-folder 35: 1)
    - Published excerpt, Catholic Digest, 1953 September (Folder 35: 2)
    - Publicity materials (Folder 35: 3)
    - Reviews (Folder 35: 4-5)
  - Address, 27th Women's Patriotic Conference on National Defense, Washington, D.C., 1953 January 30. (Folder 35: 6)
  - Radio address, 1953 July 26. (Folder 35: 7)
  - "Our Principal Ally: Superior Air Power," The Freeman, 1953 July 27. (Folder 35: 8)
  - "The Conscription Fallacy," Air Force, 1953 December. (Folder 35: 9)
  - "Notes on Fiftieth Anniversary of Powered Flight," address, San Diego, California, 1953 December 17. (Folder 35: 10)
    Typescript and clipping
  - "The Middle EastForgotten Strategic Area," World Affairs, 1954 Winter. (Folder 35: 11)
  - "Another War So Soon?" Task Force, 1954 May. (Folder 35: 12)
  - "The Strategy of Defense," speech, Texas Technological College, Lubbock, Texas, 1954 May 6. (Folder 35: 13)
  - Speech, Ninth Annual Convention, Federation of Lutheran Clubs, Washington, D.C., 1954 May 29. (Folder 35: 14)
  - "Away from Defeat," The Freeman, 1954 June 14. (Folder 35: 15)
  - Speech, Flag Day dinner, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1954 June 14
    - Correspondence (Folder 35: 16)
    - Typescript (Folder 35: 17)
    - Printed copy (Folder 35: 18)
  - Speech, Foundation to Defeat Communism, Washington, D.C., 1954 June 22. (Folder 35: 19)
  - "A Program for Asia," Human Events, 1954 August 4. (Folder 35: 20)
  - Radio interview, Mutual Broadcasting System, 1954 September 18. (Folder 35: 21)
  - Radio address, 1954 October 23. (Folder 35: 22)
  - "How to WinWithout Killing the Taxpayer," address, National Association of Real Estate Boards, Cleveland, Ohio, 1954 November 10. (Folder 35: 23)
    Correspondence, typescript, and clippings
  - "Living History," The Freeman, 1954 December. (Folder 35: 24)
  - Address, annual convention, American Coalition of Patriotic Societies, 1955 January 13. (Folder 35: 25)
  - "Atlantic Union and World Government," Task Force, 1955 May. (Folder 35: 26)
  - "The Meaning of Our Flag Today," speech, Baltimore, Maryland, 1955 June 12
    - Correspondence (Folder 35: 27)
    - Typescript (Folder 35: 28)
    - Printed copy (Folder 35: 29)
    - Clippings (Folder 35: 30)
  - "The Red Fly-By over Moscow," Human Events, 1955 June 25. (Box-folder 36: 1)
    Correspondence, typescript, printed copy, and clippings
  - "The Indirect Approach," The Freeman, 1955 August. (Folder 36: 2)
  - "NATO Supply," address, National Defense Transportation Association, Boston, Massachusetts, 1955 October 13. (Folder 36: 3)
  - "National Defense without Bankruptcy," address, Hunter College, New York City, circa 1956. (Folder 36: 4)
  - "The New Low in Eisenhower Diplomacy,", circa 1956. (Folder 36: 5)
  - Radio broadcasts, 1956. (Folder 36: 6)
  - "Only Americans Can Defend America," address, For America rally, New York City, 1956 February 22
    - Correspondence (Folder 36: 7)
    - Typescript (Folder 36: 8)
    - Printed copy (Folder 36: 9)
    - Program (Folder 36: 10)
  - "To Socialized Medicine and Socialism by Way of Universal Military Conscription," speech, annual meeting, Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, Columbus, Ohio, 1956 April 5. (Folder 36: 11)
  - "Dead Horse and Golden Shoes," The Dan Smoot Report, 1956 August 17. (Folder 36: 12)
  - "How to Have the ICBM and a Better Defense and Still Cut the Budget $10 Billion," Human Events, 1957 October 12. (Folder 36: 13)
  - "We Can Achieve Air-Space SupremacyAnd Still Save Ten Billion," radio address, Mutual Broadcasting System, 1957 December 1. (Folder 36: 14)
  - "Collective DefenseStrength or Peril?" The Dan Smoot Report, 1957 December 2. (Folder 36: 15)
  - "National Defense," address, California Cattlemen's Association, Fresno, California, 1957 December 6. (Folder 36: 16)
  - Radio address, KVOD, Denver, Colorado, 1958 January 12. (Folder 36: 17)
  - "Survival," speech, annual meeting, Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, San Francisco, California, 1958 April 10
    - Correspondence (Folder 36: 18)
    - Printed copy (Folder 36: 19)
    - Clippings (Folder 36: 20)
  - "How to Be Strong Enough to Stand Alone," Connecticut Industry, 1958 May. (Folder 36: 21)
  - "Defense, Inflation and Foreign Policy," speech, Union League Club, Chicago, Illinois, 1958 October 3. (Folder 36: 22)
  - "Psychological Warfare Can Defeat Communism," radio address, Manion Forum, 1959 January 18
    - Correspondence and clipping (Folder 36: 23)
    - Typescript (Folder 36: 24)
    - Printed copy (Folder 36: 25)
  - "Where We Stand," Air Force, 1959 March
    - Correspondence and clipping (Folder 36: 26)
    - Typescript (Folder 36: 27)
    - Printed copy (Folder 36: 28)
    - Reprint, Congressional Record, 1959 March 10 (Folder 36: 29)
  - Radio address on foreign aid, Manion Forum, 1960 March 27. (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - "AmericaFreedom's Last Bastion," speech, state conference, Daughters of the American Revolution, Toledo, Ohio, 1961 March 13 (Folder 37: 2)
  - "Aiming for Second Place," speech, annual convention, Texas Cotton Association, Dallas, Texas, 1962 March 16
    - Typescript and correspondence (Folder 37: 3)
    - Printed copy (Folder 37: 4)
    - Clippings (Folder 37: 5)
  - "The Strategy of Power Allocation," speech, Christian Freedom Foundation, New York City, 1962 May 3. (Folder 37: 6)
    Typescript and correspondence
  - Radio interview, Manion Forum, 1962 June 22. (Folder 37: 7)
  - "Foreign AidA Communist Plot to Bankrupt America," radio address, Manion Forum, 1962 July 15. (Folder 37: 8)
  - "Free World Survival," speech, annual convention, Military Order of the World Wars, Washington, D.C., 1962 October 19. (Folder 37: 9)
    Correspondence, holograph, and typescript
  - "Facing the Future,", 1963 January. (Folder 37: 10)
  - "Important 1963 Issues," Dawn, 1963 January. (Folder 37: 11)
  - "A Golden Opportunity," Spotlight, 1963 December. (Folder 37: 12)
    Holograph, typescript, and printed copy
  - "President Johnson's Golden Opportunity," radio address, Manion Forum, 1963 December 13. (Folder 37: 13)
  - "Foreign Aid is Financing Global Socialism," television interview, Manion Forum, 1964 June. (Folder 37: 14)
  - "Issues for '64Foreign Aid and Southeast Asia," radio interview, Manion Forum, 1964 June 28. (Folder 37: 15)
  - "On Character in American Youth,", 1964 September. (Folder 37: 16)
  - "Why War?", 1964 October 5. (Folder 37: 17)
  - "Facts on Foreign Aid," speech, Rotary Club, St. Louis, Missouri, 1964 November 12. (Folder 37: 18)
    Correspondence and program only
  - "Victory in Southeast Asia," Christian Economics, 1965 June 15. (Folder 37: 19)
  - Speech, United States Day celebration, Palm Beach, Florida, 1965 October 22. (Folder 37: 20)
    Correspondence, program, and typescript
  - "Victory in Viet Nam," radio address, Manion Forum, 1966 May 29. (Folder 37: 21)
  - "Some Hard Facts about Soft Money," radio address, Manion Forum, 1967 April 9. (Folder 37: 22)
  - "Impact of Foreign Aid on U.S. Industry," The Surplus Record, 1968 July. (Folder 37: 23)
  - Statement, Republican Platform Committee, Miami Beach, Florida, 1968 July 30. (Folder 37: 24)
  - "Foreign AidMilitary and Economic," Daughters of the American Revolution Magazine, 1969 January. (Folder 37: 25)
  - "The Terrors of Inflation," Viewpoints, no. 14, Institute for Monetary Research, 1972 August. (Folder 37: 26)
- Reports, Speeches, and Statements Written for Others, 1947-1952. (Box 37-38)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of nominal author
  - For Donald L. Jackson, 1949 (Folder 37: 27)
  - For Robert A. Taft
    - undated. (Folder 37: 28)
    - 1947 (Folder 37: 29)
    - 1948 (Folder 37: 30)
    - 1949 (Folder 37: 31)
    - 1950 (Folder 37: 32)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - 1952 (Folder 38: 2-3)
- Notebooks, 1941-1956. (Box 38)
  arranged chronologically
  - 1941 (Folder 38: 4)
  - 1943 (Folder 38: 5)
  - 1945 (Folder 38: 6-7)
  - 1956 (Folder 38: 8)
- Military Career File, 1918-1946. (Box 38-42)
  Correspondence, memoranda, orders, plans and reports, arranged chronologically by assignment
  - General, 1920-1946
    - Correspondence
      - undated (Folder 38: 9)
      - 1920-1930 (Folder 38: 10)
      - 1933-1939 (Folder 38: 11)
      - 1940-1941 (Folder 38: 12)
      - 1942 (Folder 38: 13)
      - 1943 (Folder 38: 14)
      - 1944 (Box-folder 39: 1)
      - 1945 (Folder 39: 2)
      - 1946 (Folder 39: 3)
    - Orders
      - 1918-1939 (Folder 39: 4)
      - 1940-1946 (Folder 39: 5)
    - Reports
      - By Fellers
        - undated (Folder 39: 6)
        - 1939 (Folder 39: 7)
        - 1941 (Folder 39: 8)
        - 1942 (Folder 39: 9)
        - 1943 (Folder 39: 10)
        - 1944 (Folder 39: 11)
        - 1945 (Folder 39: 12)
      - By others, 1939-1945 (Folder 39: 13)
  - Liaison officer, U.S. Army, Philippines
    - Correspondence, 1936-1938 (Folder 39: 14)
    - Financial report prepared by Fellers, 1937 (Folder 39: 15)
    - Materials relating to Manuel L. Quezon, 1937 (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - Proposals and reports, 1937-1938 (Folder 40: 2)
  - Instructor, Army War College, 1939
    - Course materials, 1939 (Folder 40: 3)
    - Invitation, 1939 (Folder 40: 4)
    - Lecture, 1939 (Folder 40: 5)
    - Memoranda, 1939 (Folder 40: 6)
    - Speech, 1939 (Folder 40: 7)
  - Assistant professor, U.S. Military Academy, West Point, 1939-1940
    - Correspondence, 1939 (Folder 40: 8)
    - Course materials, 1939-1940 (Folder 40: 9)
    - Lectures
      - By Fellers, 1939-1940 (Folder 40: 10)
      - By others, undated. (Folder 40: 11)
  - Military attaché, Egypt, 1940-1943
    - Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Folder 40: 12)
    - Reports
      - By Fellers, 1940-1943 (Folder 40: 13)
      - By others, 1942 (Folder 40: 14)
  - Brigadier General, Office of Strategic Services, 1943
    - Correspondence, 1943 (Folder 40: 15)
    - Memoranda, 1943 (Folder 40: 16)
  - Director of planning staff, Allied Forces, South West Pacific Area. Correspondence, 1943 (Folder 40: 17)
  - Psychological warfare officer, U.S. Army, 1944-1946 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1944 (Folder 41: 1)
    - Memoranda, 1944 (Folder 41: 2)
    - "Philippine Hour" broadcasts
      - Memorandum and transcripts, 1944 (Folder 41: 3)
      - Plans, 1944 (Folder 41: 4)
    - Plans and reports
      - Answer to Japan, 1944. (Folder 41: 5)
      - "Basic Military Plan for Psychological Warfare in the Southwest Pacific Area,", 1944 August 2. (Folder 41: 6)
      - "Report on Psychological Warfare against Japan, Southwest Pacific Area, 1944-1945,", 1946. (Folder 41: 7)
      - Miscellaneous drafts, 1944. (Folder 41: 8)
        Typescript and holograph fragments
    - Propaganda booklet, 1944 (Folder 41: 9)
    - Propaganda leaflet, 1944 (Folder 41: 10)
  - Military secretary to General Douglas MacArthur, 1944-1946
    - Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Folder 41: 11)
    - Materials relating to the Philippines
      - General, 1944-1945 (Folder 41: 12)
      - Proclamations by Sergio Osmena, undated. (Folder 41: 13)
    - Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Folder 41: 14)
    - Newsletters, 1944 (Box-folder 42: 1)
    - Official proclamations, undated. (Folder 42: 2)
  - Secretary general, Allied Council for Japan, 1946
    - Correspondence and speech, 1946 (Folder 42: 3)
    - Documents
      - Kido, Koichi. Diary excerpts and statements, 1943-1945 (Folder 42: 4)
      - Konoye, Fumimaro. Memoirs, 1946 (Folder 42: 5)
    - Summaries of proceedings
      - April 1946 (Folder 42: 6)
      - May-June 1946 (Folder 42: 7)
- Civilian Career File, 1946-1969. (Box 42-43)
  Clippings; correspondence; financial and legal records; memoranda; newsletters; press releases; printed matter; and statements, arranged chronologically by position held
  - Director of public relations, Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1946-1954
    - Clippings, 1947 (Folder 42: 8)
    - Correspondence
      - 1946 (Folder 42: 9)
      - 1947 (Folder 42: 10)
      - 1948-1954 (Folder 42: 11)
    - List of lectures given by Fellers, 1947 (Folder 42: 12)
    - Proposals, undated (Folder 42: 13)
    - Speeches, 1947
      - By Fellers, 1947 (Folder 43: 14)
      - By others, 1947-1950 (Folder 43: 15)
  - Head, Veteran Division, Republican National Committee, 1948-1954
    - Correspondence, 1948-1954 (Folder 42: 16)
    - List of materials prepared by Fellers, undated (Folder 42: 17)
    - Press releases, 1950 (Folder 42: 18)
    - Printed matter, 1948-1950 (Folder 42: 19)
    - Statement and transcript, 1949 (Folder 42: 20)
  - National director, For America, 1954-1960 (Box 43)
    - Clippings, 1954-1958 (Folder 43: 1)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Folder 43: 2)
    - Memoranda, 1956 (Folder 43: 3)
    - Printed matter, 1955-1960 (Folder 43: 4)
  - National chairman, Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 1959-1970
    - Clippings, 1963-1965 (Folder 43: 5)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Folder 43: 6)
    - Financial and legal records, 1969 (Folder 43: 7)
    - Memorandum, 1960 (Folder 43: 8)
    - Newsletters
      - 1964-1965 (Folder 43: 9)
      - 1966-1969 (Folder 43: 10)
    - Pamphlet, 1959 (Folder 43: 11)
    - Press releases, 1964-1965 (Folder 43: 12)
    - Statements, 1968 (Folder 43: 13)
- Psychological Warfare File, 1947-1955. (Box 43-45)
  Clippings, correspondence, photographs, printed matter, proposals, speeches, and writings, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Clippings, 1950-1955 (Folder 43: 14)
  - Correspondence
    - 1949 (Folder 43: 15)
    - 1950 (Folder 43: 16)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 44: 1)
    - 1952-1955 (Folder 44: 2)
  - Photographs chosen as illustrations for propaganda, undated (Folder 44: 3)
  - Printed matter
    - 1948-1950 (Folder 44: 4)